export default data = [
  {
      question: "Steve’s description of the place was so _____ that I could almost picture it in my mind.",
      options: ["bitter","vivid","sensitive","courageous"],
      correct_option: "vivid"
  },
  {
      question: "When people feel uncomfortable or nervous, they may _____ their arms across their chests as if to protect themselves.",
      options: ["toss","fold","veil","yield"],
      correct_option: "fold"
  },
  {
      question: "The doors of these department stores slide open _____ when you approach them. You don’t have to open them yourself.",
      options: ["necessarily","diligently","automatically","intentionally"],
      correct_option: "automatically"
  },
  {
      question: "Nicole is a _____ language learner. Within a short period of time, she has developed a good command of Chinese and Japanese.",
      options: ["convenient","popular","regular","brilliant"],
      correct_option: "brilliant"
  },
  {
      question: "With rising oil prices, there is an increasing _____ for people to ride bicycles to work.",
      options: ["permit","instrument","appearance","tendency"],
      correct_option: "tendency"
  },
  {
      question: "This information came from a very _____ source, so you don’t have to worry about being cheated.",
      options: ["reliable","flexible","clumsy","brutal"],
      correct_option: "reliable"
  },
  {
      question: "We hope that there will be no war in the world and that all people live in peace and _____ with each other.",
      options: ["complaint","harmony","mission","texture"],
      correct_option: "harmony"
  },
  {
      question: "To have a full discussion of the issue, the committee spent a whole hour _____ their ideas at the meeting.",
      options: ["depositing","exchanging","governing","interrupting"],
      correct_option: "exchanging"
  },
  {
      question: "While adapting to western ways of living, many Asian immigrants in the US still try hard to _____ their own cultures and traditions.",
      options: ["volunteer","scatter","preserve","motivate"],
      correct_option: "preserve"
  },
  {
      question: "With the worsening of global economic conditions, it seems wiser and more _____ to keep cash in the bank rather than to invest in the stock market.",
      options: ["sensible","portable","explicit","anxious"],
      correct_option: "sensible"
  },
  {
      question: "Under the _____ of newly elected president Barack Obama, the US is expected to turn a new page in politics and economy.",
      options: ["adoption","fragrance","identity","leadership"],
      correct_option: "leadership"
  },
  {
      question: "Rapid advancement in motor engineering makes it _____ possible to build a flying car in the near future.",
      options: ["individually","narrowly","punctually","technically"],
      correct_option: "technically"
  },
  {
      question: "When you take photos, you can move around to shoot the target object from different _____.",
      options: ["moods","trends","angles","inputs"],
      correct_option: "angles"
  },
  {
      question: "Students were asked to _____ or rewrite their compositions based on the teacher’s comments.",
      options: ["revise","resign","refresh","remind"],
      correct_option: "revise"
  },
  {
      question: "Besides lung cancer, another _____ of smoking is wrinkles, a premature sign of aging.",
      options: ["blessing","campaign","consequence","breakthrough"],
      correct_option: "consequence"
  },
]
